Guide to the Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences Department records, 1967-1995 RG0059
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences Department records
1967-1995
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Dept. of Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences
RG0059
25.5 Linear Feet
Collection includes psychology internship records, AIDS education project, conferences, correspondence, evaluations, demographic questionnaires, and quarterly reports.
Restrictions on Access
Series 1 and 4 contain restricted records.
Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records in Series 1 and 4 are closed for 100 years from date of record creation.
Clerkship records in Series 1 are closed for 75 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences Department.
Historical or Biographical Note
The George Washington University Department of Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences has a long history and proud tradition of providing state-of-the-art clinical care, outstanding education and training programs, and cutting-edge biopsychosocial research in the Nation's Capital.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include psychology internship records, the Aids education project, conferences, correspondence, policies, evaluations, demographic questionnaires, the Aids Education Program files, quarterly reports. The collection covers the years 1967-95. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into four series: Three Office files and one Internship records.
Conferences; Policies and institutions; Reports and studies; AIDS (Disease); AIDS (Disease) -- Education; Washington (D.C.); George Washington University
- Office files, 1987-1989; RG0059 Series 1; 9 Linear feet (Box 6)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains Aids Education Project data, correspondence, policies, conferences, student evaluations, clerkship evaluations. The material dates from 1987-89.
  Restrictions on Access
  Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for 100 years from date of record creation.
  Clerkship evaluations are closed for 75 years from date of record creation.
  - AIDS file System listing, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Publications, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Steuvee Billings, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - GWU psychiatric AIDS clinic, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - National Community Research Initiative, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - GWU undergraduate course, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CMSS Medical Issues Precept, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mid Atlantic AIDS Regional, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 4th International AIDS Conference: San Francisco, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photocopy, Audio-Visual: AIDS, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AIDS Education Project: Termination File, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Conferences: Announcements, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Assessment: Background, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Drafts: Evaluation Material: Assessment, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Assessment: Knowledge Questionnaire, Grand Rounds, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GWU Medical Students Questionnaire: Responses to AAMC Presentation, 12/1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - DC Medical Society: Speakers Bureau, 08/28/87 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Psychiatric Association: LSU AIDS Conference: New Orleans, 01/1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - American Psychiatric Association: New Mexico AIDS Presentation, 03/1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - American Psychiatric Association: Baylor AIDS Conference: Dallas, Texas, 07/1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - American Psychiatric Association: Presentations, Pending, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American Psychiatric Association: AIDS Education Project Steering Committee, 09/15/1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Psychiatric Association [1/3]: Commission on AIDS, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - American Psychiatric Association [2/3]: Commission on AIDS, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - American Psychiatric Association [3/3]: Commission on AIDS, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - American Psychiatric Association: AIDS Committee: Alexandria, Virginia, 07/30/1988 --07/31/1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - American Psychiatric Association: AIDS Education Committee, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - American Psychiatric Association: Committee on the Psychiatric Aspects of AIDS, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Psychiatric Section: MSDC, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - American Medical Association: Speakers Training Program, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Education Program: Technical Proposal, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Education Program: Solicitation, offer and Award, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Education Program: Business Proposal, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Education Program: Award/Contract, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Education Program: Final Training Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Education Program: Awards Announcement, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Contract: Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Contract: Finances and Audit, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Contract: Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Contract: Material, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Education Program: Request for proposal, 1986/87 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Contract Revision, 10/1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - American Psychiatric Association, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - American Psychiatric Association: AIDS Education Program, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Miami, University of, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: J Akman, MD, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Inquiries: Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Responses: Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    General note
    Thank you
  - Correspondence: AIDS, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - DC AIDS Task Force, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - AIDS Educators Directory: DC Government, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Finances, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Finance: Closing 01, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - AIDS Services, Faculty: GWU, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - CME Credits: GWU, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Committees: GWU, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Retrospective Symptomatology Study: GWU, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - BRSG Proposal Instructions: GWU, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Status, GWU Sponsored Programs, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Policies: GWU, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    AIDS, etc
  - Policies: Sponsored Programs, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - San Francisco: contractor's Meeting, 02/1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Chicago: contractor's Meeting, 07/1987 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Contractor's Meeting: Seattle, Washington, 07/1988 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - NIMH Contractor's Meeting: Los Angeles, 03/1989 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Akman, Jeffrey S., undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Frankel, Bernard L., undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Maddix, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Herzberg, Victoria L., undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Magruder, Stephen L., undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Keating, Susan C., undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Gerrity, Ellen, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Perlin, Seymour, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Soskolne PhD, Varda, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Vasquez, Kathy, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Lynn, Rusty, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Soucy PhD, Jerry, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - AIDS Project Evaluation Conference, 07/09/1987 --07/10/1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NIMH Contractors Meeting, 07/09/1987 --07/10/1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Project Evaluation Conference, 07/09/1987 --07/10/1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Contractor's Meeting, 07/09/1987 --07/10/1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - University of Washington presentation to Contractor's meeting, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Helath Education Council, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - St Elizabeth's Hospital Grand Rounds, 03/1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - St Elizabeth's Oliverhoser Day, 06/24/1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Rehabilitation Conference, GWU, 11/19/1987 --11/20/1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - National Institute of Health Regional Conference on AIDS: Panelist, 04/1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - National Institute of Health Regional Conference on AIDS: Participant, 04/1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Red Cross: AIDS/IV drug Abuse Conference, 02/27/19-02/28/1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Speaker
  - GWU AIDS Education Presentation, 05/1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - GWU Regional AIDS Conference, 09/1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Voice of America, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - AIDS: Clinical, ethical, and legal issues, 11/14/1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    MSDC and GWU
  - International Conference on AIDS: Participant, 06/01/1987 --06/05/1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - American Psychiatric Association: 142 Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Program
  - American Psychiatric Association: 142 Annual Mtg CME, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Syllabus, Proceedings, and Summary
  - American Psychiatric Association: 142 Annual Meeting New Research Program Abstracts, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - American Psychiatric Association: Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Association of Employee Assistance Program Practitioners, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - INOVA, 04/1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Pastoral Counseling, 05/1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Napas: Protection and Advocacy Systems, 06/1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - DC Bar Seminar: AIDS and the law, 06/20/1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Galludett Research Project, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Catholic University Research Project, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) Mental Health Association: Training Pending, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - University Of Maryland AIDS Training Project: Callaborative Effort, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - GW Department of Medicine: AIDS conference, St. Maarten, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown University: "Improving Physician prevention of STD and HIV infections", undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Johns Hopkins Medical Institutions, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - AIDS Sourcebook, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Community Publication, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - GW AIDS Research Proposal: Research, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Johns Hopkins Collaboration: Research, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Whitman-Walker Clinic Community Research Grant proposal, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ETC Proposal, 07/1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - National Institute of Health Nursing Ad Hoc Research Review Committee, 04/1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Research: Ruspirone, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Research Announcements: AIDS, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Health and Human Services Training Centers, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Condom Research, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - JMFAR, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Neuropsych Research: Price, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - AIDS Research Center Grants, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - AIDS Info Resources Directory, 04/1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Metropolitan Washington Directory of HIV-Related services, 03/1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Audio-Visual: Resources, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Written Material: Resources, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Agencies: Resources, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Organization: Resources, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Finances: Whitman-Walker Clinic, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Training Manual: Whitman-Walker Clinic, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Presentation: Whitman-Walker Clinic, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Subcontract: Whitman-Walker Clinic, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Operating Committee: Whitman-Walker Clinic, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Description Services, etc: Whitman-Walker Clinic, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Death and Dying Panel: GWU MS-1 Course, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Biopsychosocial Aspects of AIDS: GWU MS-1 Lecture, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - AIDS Assessment: Nurses, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 6-N Training: AIDS, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - GWU Psychiatric Resident Seminar: Training Program, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - American Psychiatric Association: Montreal, Canada: "Psychiatrist as AIDS Educators" Workshop, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - DC Bureau of School Health Services: Training Program, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Affiliated Community counselors, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - ARC Programs, 04/11/1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Arlington Count Community Mental Health, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Examples, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - American Psychiatric Association: Course on AIDS and psychotherapy, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - American Psychiatric Association: Annual Meeting, Montreal Canada, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Training Program (Pending) American Academy of Otolaryngology, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - DC Commissions of Public Health, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - GW AIDS Training Center Proposal: Pending, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - GW AIDS Training Center Proposal: support correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - AIDS and Law Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Training Grants, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Biographical Sketches, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Appendicies, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - AIDS Testing, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Teen Internships, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - AIDS Testing, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Clerkship Evaluations, 07/07/1988 - 12/15/1989 (Box 6)
    These records are closed and may not be used by the public.
- Office files, 1987-1989; RG0059 Series 2; 4.5 Linear feet
  This series contains Aids Education Program files, quarterly reports, and demographics questionnaires for students. This material is dated 1987-89.
  - NIMH Quarterly Report, 04/16/1988 --07/15/1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Quarterly Report, 10/16/1988 --01/15/1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Quarterly Report, 01/16/1989 --04/15/1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Demographics Questionnaires: Medical Students, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Financial Reports, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Reserves 01 Year: GWU AIDS Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Revised 02 Year Budget and Award: GWU AIDS Education Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Domestic Travel: Year 03, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Travel Reimbursement, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Domestic Travel: AIDS 02 Year, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CE Training, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Supplier Catalogue: University, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Budget Change Requests, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Printing and Reproduction Account, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Slides, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Reprints, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Assessment Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Postage Account, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Interdepartmental Proqurements, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Intern Assessment Questionnaire, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Marvin Center Room Requests, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Mock Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Payment Request Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Procurement Request Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Slide Order Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Store Requistions, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Travel Requests and Authorization, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Travel Itemization Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Partial Payment forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Movement Sheets, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Journal Entry Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Budget Account Cards, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Change In Status Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Conference, GWU, 12/09/1988 --12/10/1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - AIDS Conference Brochures, 12/09/1988 --12/10/1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - AIDS Conference Evaluation Materials, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - AIDS File Systems List, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Akman: CV, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Akman and Gerrity: Article, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - APA Annual Meeting, 05/07/1988 --05/13/1988 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - APA Sponsored Trips, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Brochures, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Handouts: AIDS Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Budget Revisions, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Caculator Guidebook, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Apple Computer Files, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Computer Info, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Wordperfect, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Computer Account: CAAC, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - WP Disk and File Listing, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Evaluation Questionnaire, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Letterhead: AIDS Education Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Contract Holder's Phone Numbers, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Library, Gelman: AIDS, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Library, Himmelfarb: Services, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - General memoranda, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Psychiartry Department Purchases, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Research Assistant, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Quarterly Reports: GWU AIDS Education Program, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Quarterly Reports: Whitman-Walker Clinic, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Quarterly Reports: 16 appendix, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Quarterly Reports, 05/15/1987 --08/14/1987 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Quarterly Reports, 01/15/1988 --04/15/1988 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Demographics Questionnaires: Group 2, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Office files, 1967-1988; RG0059 Series 3; 9 Linear feet
  This series contains records related to the Aids Education Project, conferences, and demographic questionnaires. This material is dated 1967-88.
  - Demographic Questionnaire, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Assessment, Knowledge, and Attitude about AIDS, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Red Cross AIDS Conference: Women and AIDS, 03/1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Red Cross Conference: Preparations, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AAMC Meeting, 12/14/1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AIDS, Sexual Assault, and Ethics: NIMH Working Meeting, 08/31/1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - APA Meeting: AIDS Workshop, 05/07/1988 --05/12/1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Walter Reed Talk: Noel, 02/16/1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Miscellaneous Requests for info, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sexual Assault and AIDS working meeting II, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 2nd Generation Contractors Meeting: Invited Speaker, 02/1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Atlanta
  - Contractor's Meeting: San Francisco, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - AIDS: Measurement of Knowledge Research Articles, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AIDS: Patient Attitudes, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - AIDS Reports, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Attitude Scale and Working with AIDS, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Assessment Packets: Earlier Versions, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Evaluation Report, 01/21/1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Evaluation Report, 11/1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - AIDS Project: Computer Information, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - AIDS Project: Original Proposal, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - APA Meeting, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Home, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - GR, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - AIDS Grant: Steinglass, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Future Assessment: AIDS Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - AIDS Undergraduate Class: S. Silver, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Ackerman Institute and AIDS, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - AMFAR, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Xerox and Office Machine, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Xerox Work: AIDS Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Trainer Article: Current Draft, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - AIDS: Media, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Train the Trainer, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Meeting at Whitman Walker, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - AIDS Journal Articles: Master file, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Attitude about People with AIDS, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Seminar on AIDS: Arlington County Department of Human Service, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Demographic Questionnaires, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Participant Log, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - General Series on AIDS, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Slides
  - AIDS Education Project Planning Notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - AIDS: Surveillance and Epidemiology, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Whitman Walker Training, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Arlington City Participant Evals, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - AIDS: APA notes and correspondence regarding evaluation material, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Whitman Walker Clinic, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Assessment: Knowledge and Attitudes about AIDS, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Data: Nurses and Nursing Students, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - AIDS: Nurse's Seminar, 12/07/1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Training: 5 South Nurses, 11/1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1st Year Medical Students, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Measures for Nurses Inservice, 03/1987 --04/1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Training: 6 North Nurses and unmatched questionnaires, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Data: Early Reports, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - AIDS and Cosmos Site Visit, 11/17/1987 --11/18/1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - HAAS Site Visit, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - AIDS: Administrative computer files, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - National Health Policy Form: Series on AIDS, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - AIDS Conference, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - AIDS: Grand Info, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - AIDS: APA, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Demographic Questionnaire, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Contractor Meeting, 01/22/1985 --01/23/1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Contractor Meeting: Chicago, Illinois, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Project Management, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Education Project Contract, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Journal Articles, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Demographic Questionnaire, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Internship records, 1993-1995; RG0059 Series 4; 3 Linear feet
  The material in this series includes psychology internship records dated 1993-1995.